<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <LootBoxTreasure.label>Hermetic Trove</LootBoxTreasure.label>
    <LootBoxTreasure.description>A trove of Hermes, the winged messenger god. Contains tremendous amount of riches and gold. Believed to be left as a gift to his worshippers and fellow travellers of the road, Hermetic boxes come in many forms, with a huge variety of contents. In some cultures Hermes is seen as mistrustful and the boxes are his ill-gotten gains, taken from the worthy. Amongst these cultures he is commonly refered to as Evri, the god of theft. </LootBoxTreasure.description>
    <LootBoxSilverSmall.label>Hermetic Box</LootBoxSilverSmall.label>
    <LootBoxSilverSmall.description>A small box of Hermes, the winged messenger god. Contains a small amount of low value items. Believed to be left as a gift to his worshippers and fellow travellers of the road, Hermetic boxes come in many forms, with a huge variety of contents. In some cultures Hermes is seen as mistrustful and the boxes are his ill-gotten gains, taken from the worthy. Amongst these cultures he is commonly refered to as Evri, the god of theft. </LootBoxSilverSmall.description>
    <LootBoxSilverLarge.label>Large Hermetic Box</LootBoxSilverLarge.label>
    <LootBoxSilverLarge.description>A large box of Hermes, the winged messenger god. Contains a large amount of low value items. Believed to be left as a gift to his worshippers and fellow travellers of the road, Hermetic boxes come in many forms, with a huge variety of contents. In some cultures Hermes is seen as mistrustful and the boxes are his ill-gotten gains, taken from the worthy. Amongst these cultures he is commonly refered to as Evri, the god of theft. </LootBoxSilverLarge.description>
    <LootBoxGoldSmall.label>Small Hermetic Chest</LootBoxGoldSmall.label>
    <LootBoxGoldSmall.description>A small chest of Hermes, the winged messenger god. Contains a small amount of high value items. Believed to be left as a gift to his worshippers and fellow travellers of the road, Hermetic boxes come in many forms, with a huge variety of contents. In some cultures Hermes is seen as mistrustful and the boxes are his ill-gotten gains, taken from the worthy. Amongst these cultures he is commonly refered to as Evri, the god of theft. </LootBoxGoldSmall.description>
    <LootBoxGoldLarge.label>Large Hermetic Chest</LootBoxGoldLarge.label>
    <LootBoxGoldLarge.description>A large chest of Hermes, the winged messenger god. Contains a large amount of high value items. Believed to be left as a gift to his worshippers and fellow travellers of the road, Hermetic boxes come in many forms, with a huge variety of contents. In some cultures Hermes is seen as mistrustful and the boxes are his ill-gotten gains, taken from the worthy. Amongst these cultures he is commonly refered to as Evri, the god of theft. </LootBoxGoldLarge.description>
    <LootBoxPandora.label>Hermetic Trials Casket</LootBoxPandora.label>
    <LootBoxPandora.description>A casket of Hermes, the winged messenger god. When opened, a random trial of Hermes will begin,which can range from small events to large, dangerous, incidents. It is believe that Hermes leaves these caskets to test his followers worthiness. </LootBoxPandora.description>
</LanguageData>