<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
    <Hemogen>water</Hemogen>
    <HemogenDesc>Water is a vital part of biological homeostatis, cruely extracted almost exclusively from living plants and animals. Occasionally it can be refined through long, complex industrial processes, with almost all wild water being too contaminated to drink. Baseliner humans cannot produce it endogenously and consume it over time in their own internal balance. Humans unable to consume water for long periods of time will be afflicted with the eventual fatal condition known as dehydration.</HemogenDesc>
    <MessagePawnHadNotEnoughBloodToProduceHemogenPack>{PAWN_nameDef} did not have enough internal water to produce a safe water pack. </MessagePawnHadNotEnoughBloodToProduceHemogenPack>
    <MessageCannotStartHemogenExtraction>{PAWN_nameDef} doesn't have enough internal water to produce a safe water pack.</MessageCannotStartHemogenExtraction>
    <AutoTakeHemogenDesc>This determines whether {PAWN_nameDef} will automatically ingest safe water packs when {PAWN_possessive} water is below {MIN}.\n\nAutomatic ingestion is currently {ONOFF}.</AutoTakeHemogenDesc>
    <ConsumeHemogenBelow>Consume water below</ConsumeHemogenBelow>
    <NeverConsumeHemogen>Never consume water.</NeverConsumeHemogen>

    <MSS_Thirst_HasForcedDehydration>Has Forced Dehydration</MSS_Thirst_HasForcedDehydration>

    <AbilityDisabledNoHemogenGene>{0_labelShort} is not a water drinker.</AbilityDisabledNoHemogenGene>
    <AbilityDisabledNoHemogen>{0_labelShort} is too dehydrated.</AbilityDisabledNoHemogen>
    <AbilityHemogenCost>Water cost</AbilityHemogenCost>
    <AbilityHemogenGain>Base water gain</AbilityHemogenGain>

    <VRE_CarryToDraincasket>Carry {0} to thirstcasket</VRE_CarryToDraincasket>

    <MSS_Thirst_ThirstCasketHediffTickRate>Interval between ticks to bump the Forced Dehydration hediff by 0.1% on the thirstcasket -> {0}ticks</MSS_Thirst_ThirstCasketHediffTickRate>

    <MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationNetLetter>Disaster! While quenching {PAWN_possessive} thirst, {PAWN_nameDef} noticed that the water net has been contaminated by a poisonous algae, which grows in environments with abundant water. {PAWN_pronoun} has purged the storage for the safety of the colony.</MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationNetLetter>
    <MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationLetter>Oh no! While quenching {PAWN_possessive} thirst, {PAWN_nameDef} looked at another {ITEM_label} and noticed that many of them have been contaminated by a corrosive algae, known to proliferate where too much water is present. The algae has eaten through {COUNT} water packs spilling their precious contents.</MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationLetter>
    <MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationLetterLabel>Water Contaminated!</MSS_Thirst_Incident_ContaminationLetterLabel>

    <MSS_Thirst_Settings>Thirst Flavour Pack</MSS_Thirst_Settings>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_MaxSafeWaterInNet>Max water in pipe net before contamination is possible</MSS_Thirst_Settings_MaxSafeWaterInNet>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_SafeWaterPacks>Max water packs on map before contamination possible</MSS_Thirst_Settings_SafeWaterPacks>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_MaxUnsafeWaterPacks>Water packs needed for highest chance of contamination</MSS_Thirst_Settings_MaxUnsafeWaterPacks>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_DaysBetweenWaterDestruction>Min days between water destruction</MSS_Thirst_Settings_DaysBetweenWaterDestruction>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_BadWaterNoticingRollsPerDay>Times per day contamination can be noticed</MSS_Thirst_Settings_BadWaterNoticingRollsPerDay>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_ArchoQuestComponentHuntInterval>Tick range for randomly generated archotech component quests</MSS_Thirst_Settings_ArchoQuestComponentHuntInterval>
    <MSS_Thirst_Settings_ArchoQuestSubQuestInterval>Tick range for the main quests subquests</MSS_Thirst_Settings_ArchoQuestSubQuestInterval>

    <GameOverArchotechInvokedIntro>You've activated the archospring. The ground rumbles. The machine whirs. The water bubbles?\n\nSuddenly the bubbles expand out like a shockwave. Once they settle, you swear the water left behind somehow looks safer. It feels safe. Like something has touched your mind to tell you "it's OK, go on, you'll be fine".\nYou test the water to see if these thoughts have any basis in reality. To your surprise, the water is safe. You check some contaminated water from your pack. It's safe too.\nCould this have been it? Did you just save the world's water?\n\n</GameOverArchotechInvokedIntro>
    <GameOverArchotechInvokedEnding>\n</GameOverArchotechInvokedEnding>
    <GameOverColonistsTranscended>A blinking prompt on a screen on one of the machines poses a question. It has cleansed the water in the immediate area, do you want to proceed to planet-wide cleansing, or maintain local only?\n\nIf you were to choose local only, you could have all the power you desired. Every colony, faction, tribe would be beholden to you for clean, safe water.\nOr you could be heroes, give the gift to the whole world, then return your old, but improved life.\n\nThese colonists have a decision to make:\n{0}</GameOverColonistsTranscended>

</LanguageData>
